loader.io 2019-06-24

# Privacy | SendGrid

SendGrid respects Your preferences concerning the collection and use of Your Personal Information. The following Privacy Policies are tailored for the different ways Personal Information is collected from individuals who visit Our web and mobile sites or apps and/or who use any of Our services or otherwise interact with Us.

  * The Website Privacy Policy addresses information We collect at Our web sites and in offline sales and marketing activities.
  * The Services Privacy Policy addresses customer data to which We may be provided access through provision of our products and services.
  * The Notice of Privacy Shield Certification page provides information about SendGrid’s certification under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework.
  * The Sub-processors page provides information about the sub-processors authorized to process customer data for SendGrid services.
  * The [Web Site Navigational Information](https://sendgrid.com/policies/privacy/website-navigational-information) page provides information about the technologies we use to collect information as individuals navigate Our Website or use Our Services and what we use this information for.

Interested in how your data is processed when you use Twilio products and services? See the [Twilio Privacy Policy](https://www.twilio.com/legal/privacy).

SendGrid uses cookies to enhance your experience. We use these for advertising and analytics purposes. By continuing to use our site, you agree to our [use of cookies](https://sendgrid.com/policies/privacy/website-navigational-information/). 

### Sign up for our newsletter to get The Scoop on product and email news.

Almost there! We just sent you an email to confirm your subscription.

We respect your privacy. Learn more about SendGrid's Privacy Policy  here and Twilio's Privacy Policy [here](https://www.twilio.com/legal/privacy)
